<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jane the Mother Fucker</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jane the Mother Fucker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 08:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Techrights is a nazi adjacent cesspool</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/techrights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 09:09:49 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/techrights/</guid>
      <description>The first fucking thing you might say about this is &amp;ldquo;No shit, fuckface, Techrights has hated Microsoft forever&amp;rdquo; and that&amp;rsquo;s the truth. But it goes much deeper than this. They don&amp;rsquo;t just hate Microsoft and other corporations that have monopolies.&#xA;It might be a little inaccurate to label the site &amp;ldquo;Nazi&amp;rdquo; too when it&amp;rsquo;s really fascist and/or Nazi adjacent. Saying something is adjacent is like saying it&amp;rsquo;s similar, but not quite the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating meat kicks ass</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/eating-meat-kicks-ass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/eating-meat-kicks-ass/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I fucking love animals&amp;hellip;. with the right seasoning.&#xA;Enjoy a picture of a stupid animal being eaten.&#xA;I was chilling in IRC eating dry roasted BBQ crickets, when some fuckface vegan started calling me a murderer.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Meat is genocide&amp;rdquo; they kept saying, over and over again, for weeks.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at the dictionary:&#xA;T he deliberate and systematic destruction of a racial, political, or cultural group</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computers are too easy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/computers-are-too-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:26:57 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/computers-are-too-easy/</guid>
      <description>Computers are too easy to use. I think Steve Jobs and Bill Gates did disservice to the computer industry. Some people are saying I&amp;rsquo;m wrong and that it&amp;rsquo;s Apple and Microsoft that made computers what they are today. I say they are wrong. Apple and Microsoft may be putting out these innovative solutions but they are not creating them.&#xA;Microsoft does not make products, it buys them and makes changes to them so they are more user friendly, insecure and inferior to competing products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Boomers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/linux-boomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/linux-boomers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to start this article off by saying that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be born in the boomer generation to be a boomer. You can be a boomer by acting like one. Hate new stuff? boomer. Run a desktop from the naughties? Boomer.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s right fuckface.&#xA;Linux Boomers are people who act like boomers because they hate new things. They thought the naughties were the pinnacle of technology and say OSS was the best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Transphobia</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/dealing-with-transphobia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 21:28:52 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/dealing-with-transphobia/</guid>
      <description>I see a lot of fucking hate aimed at the transgender community by assholes and shitheads. And sometimes these shitheads make a video of a trans person freaking out.&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t freak out. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to be put on blast by fascists.&#xA;I have a better solution.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Hello Sir, how can I help you?&amp;rdquo; says some guy&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not a Sir&amp;rdquo; says a trans woman&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t give me that gender nonsense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swearing is cruise control for cool, shithead</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/swearing-is-cruise-control-for-cool-shithead/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/swearing-is-cruise-control-for-cool-shithead/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s right, fuckface!&#xA;&amp;ldquo;uuuououououo thats offensive!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Fuck off.&#xA;There is nothing fucking wrong with using &amp;ldquo;bad words&amp;rdquo; and in fact, they add some god damned emphasis and make your use of language so much more badass.&#xA;The best music and movies are full of profanity. Rap music is cool as shit!&#xA;Can you imagine if NWA made a song called &amp;ldquo;Screw the police.&amp;rdquo; It would be fucking boring and lame. Good job Donny Osmond, idiots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Stallman loves Eugenics</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/richard-stallman-loves-eugenics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:11:10 +0000</pubDate><author>jane.arkanian@proton.me (Jane Arkanian)</author>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/richard-stallman-loves-eugenics/</guid>
      <description>I was reading some nonsense from the fuckfaces over at the Stallman Support website. They attempt to apologize for Stallman&amp;rsquo;s shitty behavior by explaining away why he is such a fucking monster.&#xA;Just take a second to read this bullshit., dipshit&#xA;First paragraph: abort fetuses that have Down&amp;rsquo;s syndrome&#xA;This is fucking eugenics bruh, plain and fucking simple. I&amp;rsquo;m not arguing about the definition of a person here motherfucker, I&amp;rsquo;m arguing against eugenics.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
